They have a plan, but not a clue.
O Brother, Where Art Thou? is a adventure, comedy,
crime film directed by Joel Coen.
In the deep south during the 1930s, three escaped convicts search for
hidden treasure while a relentless lawman pursues them.
Everett, played by George Clooney.
Pete Hogwallop, played by John Turturro.
Delmar O'Donnell, played by Tim Blake Nelson.
Big Dan Teague, played by John Goodman.
Penny, played by Holly Hunter.
Tommy Johnson, played by Chris Thomas King.
O Brother, Where Art Thou?
(released in Europe as O Brother, Where Art Thou?:  Music from the Motion Picture) is the soundtrack album of music from the 2000 American film of the same
name, written, directed and produced by the Coen Brothers and starring George Clooney, John Turturro, Tim Blake Nelson, and John Goodman.
The film is set in Mississippi during the Great Depression.
The soundtrack, produced by T-Bone Burnett, uses bluegrass, country, gospel,
blues, and Southern folk music appropriate to the time period.
With the exception of a few vintage tracks (such as Harry McClintock's 1928
single "Big Rock Candy Mountain"), most tracks are modern recordings.
The soundtrack was reissued on August 23, 2011, with 14 new tracks that were not included in the original album,
"including 12 previously unreleased cuts from music producer T-Bone Burnett's O Brother sessions."
The film explores themes of music record, country music,
based on novel or book, prophecy, southern usa.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.